Viewers, I said, whatever spirit disturbing you, be cursed, in the name of Jesus!
You familiar spirit, you evil spirit, I say to you - leave my people!
Leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen, leave my people!
You disturb their health.
You disturb their career.
You disturb their future.
You disturb their marriage.
You disturb their finances, their business.
I say, leave my people!
You evil spirit, leave my people!
In the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Where can you go from His presence?
I say, out!
That sickness, wherever it is located,
I say, wherever it is located, right now, out!
I say, out!
Wherever it's located in your blood, in your fluids, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Wherever the infirmity is located - in your blood, in your fluids, in your kidneys,
in your tendons, in your liver - right now, out!
Out!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, this is the testimony I'm declaring on you.
I'm healed! I'm delivered! I'm free!
I can hear this in my spirit.
Right now in my spirit, I can hear breakthrough.
Listen to this voice: The way out for you has come!
Listen to this voice, once again: the way out for you has come!
Before now, you were thinking, 'How will I go about it?'
I'm telling you - this is the voice of God.
Listen - I'm talking to you because you are under the influence of my voice.
Hear this voice - this is the voice of God. The way out for you has come!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
This is the voice of God.
It's not my voice; it's God's voice.
Hear this voice - the way out for you has come!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Yes, now!
Now!
Now, the way out for you has come!
I can hear breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I'm instructed to deliver this.
Not mine, not mine the voice.
Not mine, not mine the message.
The way out for you has come!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Now!
I can hear breakthrough!
Now, I can hear breakthrough.
Breakthrough, in Jesus' name!
Amen.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name